Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Scholarships (Box 143)
    - To individuals by outside agencies, 1964-1965 (Box 143)
    - Ferdandus and Elizabeth J. Payne scholarship, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Radio corporation of America, 1964-1965 (Box 143)
    - Special libraries association, 1965 (Box 143)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 143)
    - Huntsinger, 1963 (Box 143)
    - To individuals by outside agencies, 1963-1964 (Box 143)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 143)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 143)
    - To individuals by outside agencies, 1962-1963 (Box 143)
  - School of dentistry, Indianapolis, Indiana (Box 143)
    - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 143)
    - Dental law institute, proposed, 1964 (Box 143)
  - School of health, physical education, and recreation (Box 143)
    - 1962-1964, (2 folders) (Box 143)
    - Annual report, 1962-1963 (Box 143)
  - School of health, physical education, and recreation (Box 144)
    - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 144)
    - 1964-1965, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 144)
    - Annual report, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 144)
    - HPER review (Box 144)
  - School of medicine (Box 144)
    - Academic advisory committee, 1964-1965 (Box 144)
    - 1964-1965, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - I.U. Medical center 20-yearreunion, 1965 (Box 144)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - Booz, Allen, and Hamilton report on medical facilities, 1964-1965; (5 folders) (Box 144)
    - Broad program and physical plant description, 1965 (Box 144)
    - Proposals for the establishment of a second Sate Medical School, 1965 (Box 144)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 144)
    - Report or survey, 1963-1964 (Box 144)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 144)
  - School of Medicine - Indianapolis (Box 144)
    - Administrative committee, 1965-1966 (Box 144)
  - School of Medicine – Indianapolis (Box 145)
    - Administrative committee, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 145)
    - Bookstore, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 145)
    - Executive committee, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 145)
    - Booz, Allen, Hamilton report, 1963-1964 (Box 145)
    - Proposal for the establishment of the State Medical School in North Central Indiana, 1966-1968 (Box 145)
    - Reports, medical school and medical education in Indiana, 1964 (Box 145)
    - Financial control committee, 1966-1968 (Box 145)
    - Halls of residence, 1965-1967 (Box 145)
    - Future medical education in Indiana, 1966 (Box 145)
    - Heads of departments minutes, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 145)
    - Hospitals (Box 145)
      - 1963-1964, (3 folders) (Box 145)
      - Financial reports, accounting, 1968 (Box 145)
  - School of medicine – Indianapolis (Box 146)
    - Hospitals (Box 146)
      - Financial reports, 1962-1963 (Box 146)
      - Heads of departments minutes, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 146)
      - Occupancy, Long and Riley, 1964-1965 (Box 146)
      - Operating statements, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 146)
      - Write-offs and referrals to collection agency, 1965-1966 (Box 146)
    - Housing, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 146)
    - Nursing home project, 1965-1967 (Box 146)
    - Physical plant description, 1967-1968 (Box 146)
    - Purchasing, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 146)
    - Planning committee, 1962 (Box 146)
    - Registrar's correspondence, 1963 (Box 146)
    - Statistics, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 146)
    - Student union and food service building, 1963-1967; (4 folders) (Box 146)
  - School of medicine – Indianapolis (Box 147)
    - Student union and food service building, 1962-1963 (Box 147)
    - Union dormitories, 1962-1966; (3 folders) (Box 147)
    - Warthen apartments, 1962-1966; (3 folders) (Box 147)
    - Winona village housing, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 147)
  - Schr, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Schu, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Schum, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Schw, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Science advisory committee, 1963-1964; 1966; (4 folders) (Box 147)
  - Science development program, 1965 (Box 147)
  - Sco, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Sebok, Thomas A., 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 147)
  - Sei, 1962-1963 (Box 147)
  - Selective service, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 147)
  - Self-study, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 147)
  - Self-survey committee, 1966-1967 (Box 147)
  - Self study (Box 148)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 148)
    - Report, 1966 (Box 148)
    - And re-evaluation, 1965-1966 (Box 148)
    - Survey committee, 1958-1967; (3 folders) (Box 148)
  - Steering committee, 1964-1965 (Box 148)
  - Study committee, May – November 1965; (4 folders) (Box 148)
  - Se, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 148)
  - Sh, 1962-1968 (Box 148)
  - Study committee, 1965-1966; (8 folders) (Box 148)
  - USC advisory committee, 1965 (Box 148)
  - Self study committee (University study committee) (Box 149)
    - faculty files: AAUP report, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Suggestions for their consideration, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Correspondence (Box 149)
      - General, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Hull, Leroy, 1965 (Box 149)
    - A & S curriculum, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Biological sciences, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Business, school of (Box 149)
      - Curriculum, 1964 (Box 149)
      - Faculty, 1964 (Box 149)
    - Committee on curricular policies and educational programs, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Graduate school, 1965 (Box 149)
    - HPER, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Law school, 1964-1965 (Box 149)
    - Minutes of the graduate school council, 1965 (Box 149)
    - State of the university meeting, 1964 (Box 149)
    - Summer sessions, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Physical plant, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Honors program, re Chapman report, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Publications (Box 149)
      - Wall Street Journal, 1964-1965 (Box 149)
      - Examples of other alumni magazines, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 149)
    - School reports, study of academic administration, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 149)
    - Security, 1967-1968 (Box 149)
    - Task force for teaching committee, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Letters and recommendations regarding suggestion measures and various suggestions, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Memorandum sent Feb. 8 to deans, department chairmen and program directors list, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Minutes of the faculty council, 1964-1965 (Box 149)
    - Summer session (Box 149)
      - Data graphs, 1963-1968 (Box 149)
      - Student enrollment, 1964 (Box 149)
    - Letter sent to faculty (Multulith) in February of 1965 (Box 149)
    - Questionnaire sent on March 15, 1965 and list information (Box 149)
    - Memorandum sent to dean Heffner re: task force areas, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Responses to initial request, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Letter sent 5-11-65 t o25 depts., asking for return of answers to inquiries, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Programs for Big Ten institutions 4-year bach. And first professional Replies to questionnaire of March 13 (Box 149)
    - Pay advices, purchase requisitions, and other correspondence, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Wilbern, York, correspondence, 1965 (Box 149)
    - Table of content [draft], 1965 (Box 149)
    - I. Aims of the university (Box 149)
      - University as an instrument of social change, 1964-1965 (Box 149)
    - II. Student population (Box 149)
      - The influence of our admission standards and graduate requirements, 1965 (Box 149)
    - III. Programs and curricula (Box 149)
      - Academic programs, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Bloomington campus, 1964-1965 (Box 149)
      - Education, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Educational ideas, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Medicine, dentistry, and related disciplines, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Music, 1960-1963 (Box 149)
      - Regional campuses, 1965 (Box 149)
    - IV. Public service and research activities, 1965 (Box 149)
    - V. Efficiency, How are we to teach (Box 149)
      - Programs, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Faculty, 1965-1966 (Box 149)
    - VI. Size and complexity of faculty, 1965 (Box 149)
    - VII. Recruitment and retention of faculty, 1965 (Box 149)
    - VIII. [untitled] (Box 149)
      - Summer sessions, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Graduate programs, 1965 (Box 149)
    - IX. Administration and financial (Box 149)
      - Administration, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Financial, 1965 (Box 149)
    - XI. Student affairs (Box 149)
      - Academic, 1965 (Box 149)
      - Non-academic, 1965 (Box 149)
    - XII. New development and special areas, 1965-1966 (Box 149)
  - Self study committee (Box 150)
    - Final marked version of teaching report, 1965 (Box 150)
    - Responses to self-study recommendations, 1966-1967 (Box 150)
    - Growth and Change at Indiana University (Box 150)
      - Vol. 2, undated (Box 150)
      - Vol. 3, undated (Box 150)
      - Vol. 1, 1966; (3 folders) (Box 150)
      - Vol. 3, undated (Box 150)
      - Vol. 2, undated (Box 150)
  - Sen, 1964-1966 (Box 150)
  - Senior class recognition banquet, Solarium Union building, 1966 (Box 150)
  - Sesquicentennial celebration 1970 (Box 150)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 150)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 150)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 150)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 150)
      Includes "
      Edward Bellamy: Novelist and Reformer
      ," Union Worthies Number Twenty-Three, 1968
    - History, Thomas Clark, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 150)
  - Shaffer, Robert H., 1966-1968 (Box 150)
  - Shar, 1962-1968 (Box 150)
  - Shane, Harold G., 1965 (Box 150)
  - She, 1962-1968 (Box 150)
  - Shea, Edmund J., 1965-1966 (Box 150)
  - Shi, 1962-1968 (Box 150)
  - Shep, 1963-1965 (Box 150)
  - Showboat, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 150)
  - Showcase of music, inaugural dinner, 1965 (Box 150)
  - Si, 1962-1968 (Box 150)
  - Sierra Leone project, A.I.D. contract in communications media, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 151)
  - Sil, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sim, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sin, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sk, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sl, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Slavic languages and literatures, department of, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 151)
  - Sm, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Smith, 1966-1968 (Box 151)
  - Smith, George – American council of education internship, 1966-1968 (Box 151)
  - Smithwood cold storage plant, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 151)
  - Smoking, miscellaneous reports on smoking as a health hazard, 1963-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sn, 1962-1967 (Box 151)
  - Snyder, John W., The Troubles of a University, a problem paper, 1968 (Box 151)
  - So, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Soc, 1966-1968 (Box 151)
  - Social science research council, 1962-1965 (Box 151)
  - Social service, division of (Box 151)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 151)
    - Annual report, 1962-1963; 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 151)
    - Director candidates, 1965-1966 (Box 151)
  - Society for international development, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 151)
  - Sociology, 1962-1968 (Box 151)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 151)
  - Southern Indiana, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 151)
  - Sp, 1963-1966 (Box 151)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, department of, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 152)
  - Speakers, outside (Box 152)
    - Correspondence and policy, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Herbert Aptheker (Box 152)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 152)
      - Drafts of president Stahr's statements and letters, 1966 (Box 152)
      - Newspaper clippings, etc., 1966 (Box 152)
      - A-B, 1966 (Box 152)
      - C-F, 1966 (Box 152)
      - G-L, 1966 (Box 152)
      - M-P, 1966 (Box 152)
      - R-Z, 1966 (Box 152)
    - Allen Ginsburg (Box 152)
      - Poetry lecture at Ballantine Hall, March 1, 1966 (Box 152)
      - Drafts of president Stahr's statements and letters, 1966 (Box 152)
      - Poetry readings on campus, 1966 (Box 152)
    - General Lewis B. Hershey, 1966 (Box 152)
    - Vice president Hubert H. Humphrey, 1965 (Box 152)
    - Francis Keppel, 1965 (Box 152)
    - Richard M. Nixon, 1965 (Box 152)
    - Correspondence and policy, 1964-1965 (Box 152)
    - Vice-president Hubert H. Humphrey, 1965 (Box 152)
    - 1964 (Box 152)
    - Robert McNamara's proposed visit, correspondence relating to, 1963 (Box 152)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 152)
  - Special departmental lectures, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 152)
  - Speech and hearing center, 1962-1967 (Box 152)
  - Speech and theatre, 1962-1965 (Box 152)
  - Spi, 1965-1967 (Box 152)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1965-1966 (Box 152)
  - St, 1963-1967 (Box 152)
  - Staff recognition, thirteenth annual, March 21, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 153)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 153)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 153)
    - Athletic programs, 1962-1968 (Box 153)
    - Automobile, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 153)
    - Biography (Box 153)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 153)
      - Indiana Alumni Magazine, 24(9), June-July 1962 (Box 153)
      - The Quarterly Bulletin, 24(2), Spring 1962 (Box 153)
      - Res Gestae, VI(8), August 1962 (Box 153)
    - Board appointments (Box 153)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 153)
      - Board of Acacia, 1968 (Box 153)
      - Boy Scouts of America, White River Council, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 153)
      - Council for financial aid to education, Inc., 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 153)
      - Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 153)
      - Tudor Hall School board of trustees, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 153)
    - Children, 1966-1968 (Box 153)
    - Christmas gifts sent, books to state officials and others, 1962 (Box 153)
    - Christmas greetings (Box 153)
      - Received, 1962-1966; (5 folders) (Box 153)
      - Sent, 1962-1966; (5 folders) (Box 153)
    - Church, 1962-1968 (Box 153)
    - Clubs and associations; miscellaneous memberships, 1962-1968 (Box 153)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 154)
    - Committees and membership (Box 154)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 154)
      - Select committee on government research, 1964; (2 folders) (Box 154)
      - Committees on equality of educational opportunities, 1964-1965 (Box 154)
        (Includes "National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students Annual Report, 1963-1964" and A Report on the Conference on Programs to Assist Predominantly Negro Colleges and Universities Held at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, April 18 and 19, 1964"
      - Huntington College, Huntington, IN, 1963-1966; (3 folders) (Box 154)
      - Omicron Delta Kappa General Council, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 154)
      - United Health Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 154)
    - Congratulatory (Box 154)
      - Letters on presidency regret on leaving office of sec. of army, 1962 (Box 154)
      - Certificates, 1962 (Box 154)
      - The Alumni Bulletin, 45(1), November 1962 (Box 154)
      - On election as President of Indiana University, 1962; (2 folders) (Box 154)
    - Honors, awards, citations, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 154)
    - Contributions, Solicitations received and acknowledged, donations, charities, 1962-1968 (Box 154)
    - Correspondence (Box 154)
      - Letters to President Wells concerning selection of Elvis J. Stahr as president, 1962 (Box 154)
      - With Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1962 (Box 154)
      - With Lyndon B. Johnson, White House Communications, 1962-1964 (Box 154)
      - With John F. Kennedy, 1962-1963 (Box 154)
      - With Dr. Wells, 1966-1968 (Box 154)
      - With Chancellor Wells, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 154)
    - Cosmos club, 1962-1968 (Box 154)
    - Gifts (Box 154)
      - 1962-1968 (Box 154)
      - Personal, 1962-1968 (Box 154)
    - Honorary degrees – Congratulations – correspondence relating to bestowal, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 154)
    - Inauguration (Box 154)
      - 1962 (Box 154)
      - Congratulatory letters, 1962 (Box 154)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 155)
    - Inauguration (Box 155)
      - 1962 (Box 155)
      - Notes, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Replies to invitations, A-Z, (24 folders) (Box 155)
      - [Event preparation], 1962; (2 folders) (Box 155)
      - Travel, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Lists, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Sup. List and instructions, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Platform, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Sending delegate, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Programs, working copies, 1962 (Box 155)
      - Guest lists (Box 155)
        - 1962, (2 folders) (Box 155)
        - Personal lists, 1962; (2 folders) (Box 155)
        - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 155)
        - Universities, 1962 (Box 155)
        - Personal and State Legislature, 1962 (Box 155)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 156)
    - Interviews, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 156)
    - Invitations accepted, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 156)
    - Bloomington welcome dinner, 1962 (Box 156)
    - Invitations declined, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 156)
    - Invitations to speak declined, 1964-1968; (4 folders) (Box 156)
    - Invitations to speak accepted, 1962-1963; (5 folders) (Box 156)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 157)
    - Invitations declined, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 157)
    - Kentucky, 1962-1968 (Box 157)
    - Law, undated (Box 157)
    - Official entertainment (Box 157)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 157)
      - Dinner honoring Br. And Mrs. Willis Hickam, 1965 (Box 157)
      - Entertainment calendar, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 157)
    - Official gifts – Books and other gifts sent in the name of the president, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 157)
    - Oxford, 1962-1968 (Box 157)
    - Periodicals, 1962-1964; (4 folders) (Box 157)
    - Petitions, 1962 (Box 157)
    - Photographs, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 157)
    - Press criticism, 1962-1963 (Box 157)
    - Privileges, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 157)
    - Recommendations, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 157)
    - Requests, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 157)
    - Resignation from the presidency of Indiana University, 1968 (Box 157)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 158)
    - Roosevelt award nominee, 1966-1968 (Box 158)
    - Schedule, 1962-1963 (Box 158)
    - Clippings – correspondence re: press items, 1962-1968 (Box 158)
    - Scrapbook (Box 158)
      - Transactions, personal, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 158)
      - Xerox copy of items in scrapbook #1, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 158)
      - Clippings, duplicates, 1962-1963 (Box 158)
      - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 158)
    - Sigma Chi, 1962-1968 (Box 158)
    - Statements (Box 158)
      - Addresses and remarks, 1963-1967 (Box 158)
      - Demands re Dow Chemical incident, 1967 (Box 158)
      - Ex-officio, pronouncements, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 158)
      - Critical evaluation of The American Educator Encyclopedia, 1966-1968 (Box 158)
      - Resignation from I.U. Presidency, 1968 (Box 158)
      - Statement to board of trustees re dissent vs. disruption, 1968 (Box 158)
      - Graduate education in the United States, 1967 (Box 158)
      - Sunday Courier and Press, "Crisis on the Campus", 1966-1967 (Box 158)
      - Kentucky Alumnus, 1967 (Box 158)
      - On Higher education, 1966-1968 (Box 158)
      - Faculty differences – small liberal arts colleges and large institutions, 1966 (Box 158)
      - Fraternities, 1964-1965 (Box 158)
      - U.S. Savings Bonds-Payroll deductions, 1964-1965 (Box 158)
      - "What a great state university means to you", 1964 (Box 158)
    - Telephone, 1962 (Box 158)
    - Travel, 1962-1968; (7 folders) (Box 158)
    - U.S. Army, 1966-1968 (Box 158)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 159)
    - U.S. Army, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 159)
  - Stal, 1967-1968 (Box 159)
  - Standard oil, 1966-1968 (Box 159)
  - Stanford University educational council, 1962 (Box 159)
  - Star, 1962-1968 (Box 159)
  - State of the university, 1964-1968; (6 folders) (Box 159)
  - Statements of accounts, president's office copies, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 159)
  - Ste, 1962-1968 (Box 159)
  - Stern, Professor Daniel, NW Campus, undated (Box 159)
  - Stevenson, Adlai institute of international affairs, 1967 (Box 159)
  - Stew, 1962-1968 (Box 159)
  - Stillman College (Box 159)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 159)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 159)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 159)
  - Sto, 1962-1968 (Box 159)
  - Stoner, Richard B., 1963-1968 (Box 159)
  - Storerooms, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 159)
  - Str, 1962-1968 (Box 159)
  - Students (Box 159)
    - 1963-1967, (3 folders) (Box 159)
    - Nancy Dillingham case, 1964 (Box 159)
    - Student activities office, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 159)
    - Survey of political and religious attitudes, 1963 (Box 159)
  - Students (Box 160)
    - Conduct - Alcohol problems, dating, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 160)
    - Conduct – Alcohol problems, etc., 1964 (Box 160)
    - Conduct - Alcohol problems, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 160)
    - Conduct - Alcohol problems, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 160)
    - Demonstrations (Box 160)
      - Cuba, 1962 (Box 160)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 160)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 160)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 160)
    - Employment
      - 1962-1963 (Box 160)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 160)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 160)
      - 1966 (Box 160)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 160)
    - Faculty discussions, Viet-Nam 'Teach-in," demonstrations, opinions expressed, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 160)
    - Faculty discussions, Vietnam, 1966-1968 (Box 160)
    - Faculty retreat, Bradford Woods, 1967 (Box 160)
    - Faculty - Vietnam demonstration, Dean Rusk-Dow Chemical demonstrations
      - Faculty responses, 1967 (Box 160)
      - General, 1967 (Box 160)
      - Letters answered by pres. Stahr, 1967-1968 (Box 160)
      - R.H. Shaffer statement, November 8, 1967 (Box 160)
      - Controversial Dow and Rusk materials, 1967-1968 (Box 160)
    - Open forum, 1967 (Box 160)
    - Forum, material used, April 26, 1967; 1966-1967; 1 Folder Folder 1 of 3 (Box 160)
    - Forum, material used, April 26, 1967; 2 Folder Folder 2 of 3 (Box 160)
    - Forum, material used, April 26, 1967; 3 Folder Folder 3 of 3 (Box 160)
    - Government (Box 160)
      - Letter of student body president on Indiana Anti-Secrecy Act, 1967 (Box 160)
      - Letter of student body president on All-Events building, 1967 (Box 160)
      - Student senate minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 160)
      - July 1966-May 1967 (Box 160)
  - Students (Box 161)
    - Government (Box 161)
      - Survey re: Open visitation, choice of domicile, alcoholic beverages, 1968 (Box 161)
      - Officers and leaders, 1963-1964 (Box 161)
      - 1962-1966, (4 folders) (Box 161)
      - Annual report, 1962-1963; 1968; (2 folders) (Box 161)
    - Health center (Box 161)
      - Radio emergency communications system for civil defense, 1966 (Box 161)
      - Annual report, 1962-1963; 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box 161)
      - Service, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 161)
      - Annual report, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 161)
    - Insurance, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 161)
    - Loans (Box 161)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 161)
      - United student aid funds (Box 161)
        - Ashville, North Carolina, October 20-22, 1968 (Box 161)
        - Biloxi, Mississippi, March 1968 (Box 161)
        - Tuxedo, New York, October 23-24, 1967 (Box 161)
      - 1962-1966, (4 folders) (Box 161)
  - Student (Box 162)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 162)
    - News articles and correspondence, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 162)
    - Organizations (Box 162)
      - Accounts, 1967-1973 (Box 162)
      - Correspondence #1-2, 1962-1971; (2 folders) (Box 162)
      - 1959-1974, (7 folders) (Box 162)
      - Annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 162)
      - A.W.S., 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 162)
      - Dubois club, president Stahr's correspondence, A-B, C-F, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 162)
  - Student Organizations (Box 163)
    - Dubois club (Box 163)
      - President Stahr's correspondence, G-Z, 1966; (6 folders) (Box 163)
      - Drafts of president Stahr's statements and letters, 1966 (Box 163)
      - Letters dealing with Ginsberg, Aptheker, 1966 (Box 163)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 163)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 163)
    - OUR, YAF and others, 1965-1967 (Box 163)
      Scope and Content Note